[
    {
      "question": "What is the mean of these numbers:<br> [71, 72, 73, 74, 75, 76, 77, 78]?",
      "correctAnswer": "74",
      "options": [
        "73",
        "74",
        "75",
        "76"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mean of these numbers:<br> [72, 73, 74, 75, 76, 77, 78, 79]?",
      "correctAnswer": "75",
      "options": [
        "74",
        "75",
        "76",
        "77"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mean of these numbers:<br> [73, 74, 75, 76, 77, 78, 79, 80]?",
      "correctAnswer": "76",
      "options": [
        "75",
        "76",
        "77",
        "78"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mean of these numbers:<br> [74, 75, 76, 77, 78, 79, 80, 81]?",
      "correctAnswer": "77",
      "options": [
        "76",
        "77",
        "78",
        "79"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mean of these numbers:<br> [75, 76, 77, 78, 79, 80, 81, 82]?",
      "correctAnswer": "78",
      "options": [
        "77",
        "78",
        "79",
        "80"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mean of these numbers:<br> [76, 77, 78, 79, 80, 81, 82, 83]?",
      "correctAnswer": "79",
      "options": [
        "78",
        "79",
        "80",
        "81"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mean of these numbers:<br> [77, 78, 79, 80, 81, 82, 83, 84]?",
      "correctAnswer": "80",
      "options": [
        "79",
        "80",
        "81",
        "82"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mean of these numbers:<br> [78, 79, 80, 81, 82, 83, 84, 85]?",
      "correctAnswer": "81",
      "options": [
        "80",
        "81",
        "82",
        "83"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mean of these numbers:<br> [79, 80, 81, 82, 83, 84, 85, 86]?",
      "correctAnswer": "82",
      "options": [
        "81",
        "82",
        "83",
        "84"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mean of these numbers:<br> [80, 81, 82, 83, 84, 85, 86, 87, 88]?",
      "correctAnswer": "84",
      "options": [
        "83",
        "84",
        "85",
        "86"
      ]
    }
]